AD.MC.031
AbuDhabi
- Al Qassim Family Collection Prints (Object AD_MC_031_ref168)
  - View of Khor Dubai from above. 6.3 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref94)
    Arabic Writing; Architecture; Boats/Ships; Buildings; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Water
  - Landscape of Bur Dubai. 6.3 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref95)
    Arabic Writing; Architecture; Boats/Ships; Buildings; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Landscapes; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Ships; Water
  - Landscape view of Khor Dubai. 6.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref96)
    Arabic Writing; Architecture; Boats/Ships; Buildings; Clouds; Construction; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Landscapes; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Ships; Water
  - View of Khor Dubai. 6.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref97)
  - Houses at the edge of Khor Dubai. 6.6 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref98)
    Arabic Writing; Architecture; Boats/Ships; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Ships; Water
  - Umm Al-Quwain from a far. 6.7 x 9.0 cm, 25 February 1965; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref99)
    Arabic Writing; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Umm Al-Quwain, United Arab Emirates; Water
  - Landscape of mountains in Masafi, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.8 x 8.8 cm, 25 February 1965; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref100)
    Agriculture; Animals; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Mountains; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Trees
  - Desert in Al-Dhaid, Sharjah. 6.5 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref101)
    Arabic Writing; Countryside/Rural; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Nature; Photographic Prints; Plants; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates
  - Landscape of the desert in Al-Dhaid. 6.3 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref102)
    Arabic Writing; Countryside/Rural; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Nature; Photographic Prints; Plants; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Trees
  - Al-Salehia, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.4 x 8.7, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref103)
    Arabic Writing; Clouds; Countryside/Rural; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Mountains; Photographic Prints; Plants; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates
  - Landscape of Al-Salehia. 6.4 x 6.7 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref104)
    Arabic Writing; Clouds; Countryside/Rural; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Plants; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates
  - View of Khatt, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref105)
    Agriculture; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Landscapes; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Plants; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Trees
  - Mushrif Area, Dubai. 6.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref106)
    Arabic Writing; Clouds; Deserts; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Dunes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Plants; Sand; Trees
  - Al-Dhaid desert, Sharjah. 6.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref107)
    Arabic Writing; Deserts; Dunes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Plants; Sand; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Trees
  - Farm in Al-Dhaid, Sharjah. 6.3 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref108)
    Agriculture; Arabic Writing; Date palms; Farms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Plants; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Trees
  - Landscape of Al-Dhaid, Sharjah. 6.3 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref109)
    Agriculture; Arabic Writing; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Mountains; Photographic Prints; Plants; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Trees
  - Shinas, Oman. 6.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref110)
    Arabic Writing; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Mountains; Oman; Photographic Prints; Sand; Trees
  - Landscape of Al Kharran desert in Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref111)
    Arabic Writing; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Plants; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Sand; Trees
  - Man in front of the sea with Umm Al-Quwain in the background. 6.8 x 9.0 cm, 25 February 1965; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref112)
    Arabic Writing; Beaches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Men; Persian Gulf; Photographic Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Umm Al-Quwain, United Arab Emirates; Water
  - Al-Salehia desert, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.5 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref113)
    Arabic Writing; Countryside/Rural; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Plants; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Trees
  - Desert in Al-Dhaid, Sharjah. 6.3 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref114)
    Arabic Writing; Countryside/Rural; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Plants; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Trees
  - A goat in an old house in Deira, Dubai. 6.6 x 8.7 cm, Circa 1960-1969; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref115)
    Animals; Arabic Writing; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Photographic Prints
  - Official portrait of Sabah Salem Al Mubarak Al Sabah Emir of Kuwait. 8.8 x 6.7 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref116)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Men; Officials; Photographic Prints
  - Portrait of Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum. 8.8 x 6.7 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref117)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Officials; Photographic Prints; Sheikhs
  - Men and boys walking during Sheikh Rashid's reception at the Dubai airport. 4.9 x 7.1 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref118)
    Airports; Arabic Writing; Boys; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Sheikhs; Walking
  - Group of men waiting during Sheikh Rashid's reception at the Dubai Airport. 5.2 x 7.3 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref119)
  - View of Khor Dubai from above. 6.7 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref120)
    Arabic Writing; Architecture; Boats/Ships; Buildings; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Landscapes; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Water
  - Al Kharran, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.7 x 8.7 cm, 8 March 1962; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref121)
    Animals; Arabic Writing; Countryside/Rural; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Plants; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Trees
  - Group of men in the Al Kharran desert. 6.6 x 8.6 cm, 8 March 1962; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref122)
    Arabic Writing; Countryside/Rural; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Plants; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Sand; Trees
  - Group of men welcoming Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum at the Dubai Airport. 5.0 x 7.1 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref123)
  - Men greeting Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum at the Dubai Airport. 5.3 x 7.4 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref124)
  - Boys swimming in Khatt Spring, Ras Al Khaimah. 6.0 x 5.9 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref125)
    Arabic Writing; Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Rocks; Springs; Trees; Water
  - Farm in Al Salehia, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref126)
    Agriculture; Arabic Writing; Cars; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Plants; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Trees
  - A man shaking hands with Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum at the Dubai Airport. 5.1 x 7.1 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref127)
  - A group of men at the Dubai Aiport for Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum's reception. 5.3 x 7.2 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref128)
    Airplanes; Airports; Arabic Writing; Cars; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Sheikhs; Traditional Dress
  - A group of men disembarking an Iran Air plane at the Dubai Airport. 5.1 x 7.3, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref129)
  - Group of men at the Dubai Aiport during Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum's Reception. 5.3 x 7.3 cm, 1965; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref130)
  - A man holding a child at the Dubai Airport during Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum's reception. 5.1 x 7.2 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref131)
    Airports; Arabic Writing; Babies; Boys; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Sheikhs
  - Date palm trees in Filli, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.8 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref132)
    Arabic Writing; Countryside/Rural; Date palms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates
  - Two men in Khatt, Ras Al Khaimah. 8.7 x 6.6 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref133)
    Agriculture; Arabic Writing; Cameras; Date palms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Irrigation system; Men; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Plants; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Water
  - Boys by the irrigation system in Al Salehia, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.5 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref134)
    Agriculture; Arabic Writing; Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Irrigation system; Photographic Prints; Plants; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Water
  - Desert of Al Kharran, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.6 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref135)
    Arabic Writing; Countryside/Rural; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Plants; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Sand; Trees
  - Khatt, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.5 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref136)
    Arabic Writing; Countryside/Rural; Gelatin Silver Prints; Mountains; Photographic Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Rocks; Trees
  - Landscape of Al Salehia, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.6 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref137)
    Arabic Writing; Countryside/Rural; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Mountains; Photographic Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Trees
  - Men working on a construction in Al-Dhaid. 6.4 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref138)
    Arabic Writing; Construction; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates
  - Boy posing behind tobacco plants in Al Salehia, Ras Al-Khaimah. 8.7 x 6.2 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref139)
    Agriculture; Arabic Writing; Boys; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Plants; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Tobacco; Trees
  - Two men next to a truck in Khatt, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.6 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref140)
    Arabic Writing; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Trips; Trucks
  - View from a mosque in Khor Dubai. 6.4 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref141)
  - Landscape of Dubai from above. 6.3 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref142)
    Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Landscapes; Palm trees; Photographic Prints
  - Landscape of Al-Dhaid, Sharjah. 6.8 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref143)
    Arabic Writing; Countryside/Rural; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Sand; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Trees
  - View of houses in Dubai. 6.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref144)
    Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Water
  - View of Dubai from Bur Dubai. 6.3 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref145)
    Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Landscapes; Photographic Prints
  - View of the Arabian Gulf, Dubai. 6.7 x 8.6 cm, 25 August 1964; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref146)
    Boats/Ships; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Men; Persian Gulf; Photographic Prints; Water
  - Men inside tent in Al Salehia, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.3 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref147)
    Arabic Writing; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Tents
  - Mountains in Masafi, Dubai. 6.8 x 8.9 cm, 25 February 1965; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref148)
    Arabic Writing; Date palms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Mountains; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates
  - Group of men on a trip in Al Kharran, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref149)
    Arabic Writing; Countryside/Rural; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Plants; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Tents; Trips
  - Crowd surrounding a car during Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum's reception at the Dubai Airport. 6.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref150)
    Airports; Arabic Writing; Cars; Crowds; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Sheikhs; Traditional Dress
  - Two boys in front of a tent in Al Dhaid, Sharjah. 6.7 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref151)
    Arabic Writing; Boys; Countryside/Rural; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Tents
  - Landscape of Khatt, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.5 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref152)
    Arabic Writing; Countryside/Rural; Date palms; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Landscapes; Mountains; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Rocks; Trees
  - A car in front of a crowd of men during Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum's reception at the Dubai Airport. 8.8 x 6.6 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref153)
    Airports; Arabic Writing; Cars; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Sheikhs; Traditional Dress
  - A minaret of a mosque in Dubai. 6.4 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref154)
    Arabic Writing; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Minaret; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Towers
  - A water tank in Dubai. 6.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref155)
  - View of stores in Deira, Dubai. 6.3 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref156)
    Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Shops
  - Men swimming in the hot springs in Khatt, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.6 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref157)
    Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Rocks; Springs; Swimming; Water
  - Landscape of the coast of Oman. 8.8 x 6.8 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref158)
    Arabic Writing; Beaches; Coast; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Oman; Photographic Prints; Sand; Seas; Water
  - Man inside tower of Khatt, Ras Al-Khaimah. 8.6 x 6.7 cm, 25 August 1964; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref159)
    Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Towers
  - Crowd of people during Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum's reception at the Dubai Airport. 6.7 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref160)
    Airports; Arabic Writing; Boys; Crowds; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Police; Sheikhs; Traditional Dress
  - View of the sea on the road between Dubai and Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.7 x 8.7, Undated; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref161)
    Arabic Writing; Beaches; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Seas; Water
- Al Qassim Family Collection Films (Object AD_MC_031_ref163)
- Al Qassim Family Collection Negatives (Object AD_MC_031_ref162)